Portia K. Maultsby Collection, 1981-1986.
Indiana University Digital Library Program
Portia K. Maultsby Collection
1981-1986
Indiana University, Archives of African American Music and Culture (AAAMC) Smith Research Center, Rooms 180-181 2805 E. 10th St. Bloomington, IN 47408-2601 Phone: 812-855-8547 Fax: 812-856-0333 Email: aaamc@indiana.edu http://www.indiana.edu/~aaamc
Maultsby, Portia K.
SC 18G
169 audiocassettes: analog, stereo + 5 document cases
Series G, "Music Industry Interviews," consists of transcripts and audiocassettes of interviews primarily conducted by Portia K. Maultsby between 1981-1986 as part of her research on the Black music industry. The remainder of the series in this collection are still in the process of being accessioned and are unavailable for general research and public use.
Access Restrictions
Reference copies and transcripts for most, but not all, of the audiocassettes in Series G, "Music Industry Interviews," are available for in-house use at the Archives of African American Music and Culture, Indiana University. Please refer to the information included under each interview for details. If you would like to access an item without a reference copy and/or transcript, please contact our staff well in advance of your visit for details.
Biographical Note
Portia K. Maultsby received a Ph.D. degree in Ethnomusicology from the University of Wisconsin--Madison, and is a professor emeritus in the Department of Folklore and Ethnomusicology, the former director of the Archives of African American Music and Culture, and a former adjunct professor of African American and African Diaspora Studies at Indiana University. She teaches historical and theoretical courses on African American music and culture in ethnomusicology. Her research topics have centered on Black religious and popular music and she has lectured and conducted workshops throughout the United States, as well as in England, The Netherlands, Russia, Cuba, Zimbabwe, and Malawi. She is co-editor of African American Music: An Introduction, (Routledge Press, 2006). She also has served as consulting scholar for PBS, BBC, and NPR productions on African American music. In addition to her scholarly work, Professor Maultsby is a keyboard player and the founding director of the IU Soul Revue, a touring ensemble specializing in the performance of African American popular music.
Arrangement
Currently organized into one series and the following subseries:
Subseries 1. Interviews by Maultsby, 1979-1989
Subseries 2. Interviews by Various Interviewers and Miscellaneous Recordings, 1979-1989
Each subseries is arranged alphabetically by interviewee's last name or the title in the case of non-interviews.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of 168 audiocassette recordings of interviews; complete or partial transcripts are available for many. The bulk of the interviews (138 cassettes) were conducted in person by Maultsby between 1981-1986 as part of her research on the Black music industry. The interviews provide an aural documentation of the history and development of rhythm and blues music through the personal narratives of musicians, composers, producers, deejays, and record company executives. In particular, Maultsby's interviews trace the emergence of Black music divisions and the promotion of Black artists by major record labels. Other significant issues emphasized in the discussions are cultural identity, gender, appropriation, aesthetics, and the racially defined politics and marketing practices of the industry. Of equal importance are the stories told by musicians who profoundly shaped the development of rhythm and blues while redefining the direction of American popular music.
All interviews were conducted by Maultsby unless otherwise indicated.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in IUCAT, the IU Libraries' online catalog. Materials about related topics, persons or places can be found by searching the catalog using these terms.
Names
Alstin, Frank
Bailey, Lee, 1947-
Barnes, John
Barnum, Billie
Barnum, H. B.
Bartholomew, Dave
Bears, Sandra
Bell, Al
Byrd, Bobby, 1934-2007
Clark, Dave, 1942-
Davis, Richard
Fields, Richard "Dimples", 1941-2000
Foster, William P. (William Patrick)
Francis, Panama
Gamble, Kenny
Harris, Bill, 1916-1973
Henderson, Jocko
Higgins, Monk
Holeman, Jerry
Holland, Brian
Johnson, Evelyn
Jones, Shirley (Vocalist)
King, Alonzo
Lanier, Warren
Love, Billye
Love, Darlene
Love, Walt
Maults-By, Carl
McCoy, Sid
McRae, Joyce
Medlin, Joe
Moore, Sam, 1935-
Otis, Johnny, 1921-2012
Ott, Horace
Parker, Deanie
Reed, Tom
Rich, Jai
Rifkind, Jules
Rifkind, Roy
Roberts, Virgil
Roebuck, Richard
Russell, Albert, 1933-
Sanjek, Russell
Shaw, Larry
Silverman, Tom
Simms, Winki
Sims, August
Smith, Frankie
Smith, John
Stevenson, Mickey
Stone, J. B.
Stone, Jesse
Taylor, H. LeBaron, 1935-2000
Thomas, Carla, 1942-
Thomas, Rufus, 1917-2001
Todd, David
Toussaint, Allen
Troutman, Larry, 1944-1999
Vickers, Carle
Ware, George
Waters, Maxine
Westbrooks, Logan H.
White, Granville
Wiggins, Willie
Williams, Deniece
Williams, Jean
Williams, Myrna
Witherspoon, Jimmy
Wonder, Stevie
Young, Earl
Topics
African American musicians
Rhythm and blues musicians
African American sound recording executives and producers
Stax Records
Philadelphia International Records
Motown Record Corporation
Soul musicians
African American disc jockeys
Interviews (Sound recordings)
Oral histories
Administrative Information
Acquisition Information
Donated by Portia K. Maultsby in 2008.
Collection Inventory
- Music Industry Interviews, 1979-1989, 169 audiocassettes: analog, stereo + documentation
  - 1. Interviews by Maultsby, 1979-1989, 138 audiocassettes (9,106 minutes): analog, stereo + documentation
    - Abner, Ewart, 1984 October 21, INT 1A--INT 1B; cass 1233--cass 1234; 2 audiocassettes (91 minutes) + 1 transcript (62 typed leaves)
      Content
      Interview with Ewert Abner, manager for Stevie Wonder and former president of Vee-Jay and Motown Records, recorded in Santa Monica, California.
      Pagination for transcript skips page 39. The last 3 minutes of cass 1234, side A and all of side B contain a broadcast radio program about Janus Joplin.
      Reference Copies
      Preservation master file(s): 24 bit/96 kHz Broadcast Wave File (BWF)
      Production master file(s): 16 bit/44.1 kHz Broadcast Wave File (BWF)
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 41--CDREF 42
    - Allen, Henry, 1982 November 1, INT 2A--INT 2B; cass 1235--cass 1236; 2 audiocassettes (133 minutes) + 1 transcript (45 typed leaves)
      Interview with Henry Allen, record executive for Atlantic Records; recorded in New York, New York.
      Interview also has a second, partial transcript (23 leaves).
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 43--CDREF 45
    - Allen, Hoss, 1984 September 7, INT 3A--INT 3B; cass 1237--cass 1238; 2 audiocassettes (134 minutes) + 1 transcript (68 typed leaves)
      Interview with William "Hoss" Allen, disc jockey for WLAC, Nashville; recorded in Nashville, Tennessee.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 46--CDREF 48
    - Alstin, Frank, 1982 November 24, INT 4; cass 1239; 1 audiocassette (84 minutes) + 1 transcript (23 typed leaves)
      Interview with Frank Alstin, producer, songwriter, and vocalist; recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 49--CDREF 50
    - Bailey, Lee, 1983 May 28, INT 86; cass 1367; 1 audiocassette (88 minutes) + 1 transcript (30 typed leaves)
      Interview with Lee Bailey, former air personality, owner of Lee Bailey Productions, and broadcast executive and host for RadioScope; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 225--CDREF 226
    - Barnes, John, 1983 March 16, INT 6; cass 1241; 1 audiocassette (59 minutes) + 1 transcript (25 typed leaves)
      Interview with John Barnes, arranger, songwriter, producer, and keyboardist; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 52
    - Barnum, Billie, 1983 March 9, INT 66; cass 1346; 1 audiocassette (92 minutes) + 1 transcript (46 typed leaves)
      Interview with Billie Barnum, session vocalist; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 203--CDREF 204
    - Barnum, H. B., 1983 March 8, INT 77; cass 1357; 1 audiocassette (63 minutes) + 1 transcript (31 typed leaves)
      Interview with H.B. Barnum, arranger, producer, and musical director for Motown Records; recorded in Hollywood, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 210
    - Bartholomew, Dave, 1985 May 14, INT 7; cass 1242; 1 audiocassette (41 minutes) + 1 transcript (30 typed leaves)
      Interview with David Bartholomew, songwriter, arranger, and producer; recorded in New Orleans, Louisiana.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 53
    - Bears, Sandra, 1984 October 26, INT 81; cass 1361; 1 audiocassette (40 minutes) + 1 transcript (14 typed leaves)
      Interview with Sandra Bears, vocalist for The Jewels and The James Brown Show; recorded in Washington, DC.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 215
    - Bell, Al, 1983 May 26, INT 8A--INT 8B; cass 1243--cass 1244; 2 audiocassettes (183 minutes) + 1 transcript (71 typed leaves) and supplementary materials
      Interview with Al Bell, record executive for Stax Records; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Supplementary materials consist of photocopies of news clippings about Bell and the Staples singers.
      Pagination for transcript for cass 1244 includes 3 and 3a.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 54--CDREF 57
    - Byrd, Bobby, 1984 September 8, INT 9A--INT 9D; cass 1245--cass 1247, cass 1248 (dup); 3 audiocassettes (253 minutes) + 1 transcript (130 typed leaves)
      Interview with Bobby Byrd, vocalist for James Brown and the Famous Flames; recorded in Nashville, Tennessee.
      Pagination for transcript for cass 1248 uses page 34 twice; cass 1248 and part of cass 1247, side B, are duplicates of cass 1245--cass 1247.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 58--CDREF 63; CDREF 65
    - Cameron, Daryl, 1982 November 24, INT 10A--INT 10B; cass 1249--cass 1250; 2 audiocassettes (116 minutes) + 1 transcript (50 typed leaves)
      Interview with Daryl Cameron, A&R, producer, and songwriter for Philly World; recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 66--CDREF 68
    - Clark, Dave, 1983 April 9, INT 11A; cass 1251; 1 audiocassette (91 minutes) + 1 transcript (31 typed leaves)
      Interview with Dave Clark, pioneering music promoter; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 69--CDREF 70
    - Clark, Dave, 1983 April 10, INT 11B--INT 11C; cass 1252--cass 1253; 2 audiocassettes (104 minutes) + 1 transcript (31 typed leaves); Maultsby, Portia K.; B.R.E.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 71--CDREF 72
    - Clark, Dave [lecture], 1983 April 10, INT 12; cass 1254; 1 audiocassette (83 minutes) + 1 transcript (22 typed leaves)
      Lecture by Dave Clark, pioneering music promoter, presented to Michael Frisby's Entertainment Law class, with questions from Portia K. Maultsby; recorded at the University of West Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 73--CDREF 74
    - Davis, Richard
      SEE: Holland, Brian, Eddie Holland, and Richard Davis.
    - Dockery, Bob, 1983 April 20, INT 88; cass 1369; 1 audiocassette (46 minutes) + 1 transcript (17 typed leaves)
      Interview with Bob Dockery, owner and president of Syndicate It, Inc.; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 228
    - Fields, Richard "Dimples," 1983 March 2, INT 13A--INT 13B; cass 1255--cass 1256; 2 audiocassettes (184 minutes) + 1 transcript (64 typed leaves)
      Interview with Richard "Dimples" Fields, songwriter and vocalist; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 75--CDREF 78
    - Fields, Rochelle, undated, INT 89; cass 1370; 1 audiocassette (92 minutes) + 1 transcript (35 typed leaves)
      Interview with Rochelle Fields, music publisher for Chrysalis Publishing; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 229--CDREF 230
    - Foster, Louise, 1983 May 11, INT 14; cass 1257; 1 audiocassette (46 minutes) + 1 transcript (17 typed leaves)
      Interview with Louise Foster, air personality and disc jockey for KJLH Radio; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 79
    - Foster, William, 1983 October 20, INT 65; cass 1345; 1 audiocassette (33 minutes) + 1 transcript (14 typed leaves) and supplementary material
      Interview with Dr. William Foster, Director of Bands for Florida A&M University; recorded in Tallahassee, Florida.
      Supplementary material consists of the following article: Malone, Jacqui. 1990. "The FAMU Marching 100." Black Perspective in Music 18(1-2): 59-80.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 202
    - Francis, David "Panama," 1983 December 31, INT 15A--INT 15C; cass 1258--cass 1260; 3 audiocassettes (144 minutes) + 1 transcript (66 typed leaves), correspondance (2 typed leaves), and résumé (5 typed leaves)
      Interview with David "Panama" Francis, drummer; recorded in Orlando, Florida.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 80--CDREF 82
    - Frisby, Michael, 1983 April 8, INT 17; cass 1264; 1 audiocassette (71 minutes) + 1 transcript (24 typed leaves)
      Interview with Michael Frisby, entertainment attorney and former radio program director; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Pagination for transcript skips page 5.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 86
    - Gamble, Kenny, 1982 September 18, INT 90; cass 1371; 1 audiocassette (42 minutes)
      Interview with Kenny Gamble, songwriter for Philadelphia International Records (PIR); recording location unknown.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 231
    - Gilbert, Carrie, 1982 November 4, INT 18A--INT 18C; cass 1265--cass 1267; 3 audiocassettes (207 minutes) + 1 transcript (73 typed leaves)
      Interview with Carrie Gilbert, songwriter for Philadelphia International Records (PIR); recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 87--CDREF 91
    - Graham, Michael, 1984 October 26, INT 80; cass 1360; 1 audiocassette (46 minutes) + 1 transcript (21 typed leaves)
      Interview with Michael Graham, former MC for the Howard Theatre; recorded in Washington, DC.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 214
    - Harris, Bill, 1984 October 9, INT 69; cass 1349; 1 audiocassette (64 minutes) + 1 transcript (23 typed leaves)
      Interview with Bill Harris, guitarist for the Clovers vocal group; recorded in Washington, DC.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 208
    - Harris, Norman, 1982 October 26?, INT 19A--INT 19B; cass 1268--cass 1269; 2 audiocassettes (156 minutes) + 1 transcript (40 typed leaves)
      Interview with Norman Harris, guitarist, producer, and writer for Philadelphia International Records (PIR); recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Date is listed as October 26, 1982 on cassette, but as Nov. 15, 1982 on the matching transcript.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 92--CDREF 95
    - Henderson, Douglas "Jocko," 1982 December 22, INT 20; cass 1270; 1 audiocassette (44 minutes) + 1 transcript (19 typed leaves) and press release (3 typed leaves)
      Interview with Douglas "Jocko" Henderson, radio announcer and acknowledged creator of "rap"; recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 96
    - Higgins, Monk, 1983 May 31, INT 60; cass 1338; 1 audiocassette (87 minutes) + 1 transcript (36 typed leaves) and résumé (4 typed leaves)
      Interview with Monk Higgins, arranger, composer, and producer; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Pagination for transcript skips page 36 (i.e., last page is 37).
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 191--CDREF 192
    - Holeman, Jerry, 1984 September 27, INT 21A--INT 21B; cass 1271--cass 1272; 2 audiocassettes (133 minutes) + 1 transcript (68 typed leaves)
      Interview with Jerry Holeman, songwriter and vocalist for the Orioles vocal group; recorded in Washington, DC.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 97--CDREF 99
    - Holland, Brian, Eddie Holland, and Richard Davis, 1983 April 29, INT 22; cass 1273; 1 audiocassette (90 minutes) + 1 transcript (37 typed leaves) and supplementary materials
      Interview with Brian and Eddie Holland, independent songwriters and former staff writers for Motown Records, and Richard Davis, attorney; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Supplementary materials include an analysis of "Ask Any Girl" and photocopies of news clippings.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 100--CDREF 101
    - Johnson, Evelyn, 1985 May 12, INT 23A--23B; cass 1274--cass 1275; 2 audiocassettes (72 minutes) + 1 transcript (51 typed leaves)
      Interview with Evelyn Johnson, record executive for Duke-Peacock Records; recorded in Houston, Texas.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 102--CDREF 103
    - Jones, Regina, 1983 March 11, INT 24; cass 1276; 1 audiocassette (49 minutes) + 1 transcript (31 typed leaves)
      Interview with Regina Jones, publisher and owner of Soul magazine; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      A second, partial transcript of this interview also exists (8 leaves).
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 103
    - Jones, Shirley, 1983 March 9, INT 25; cass 1277; 1 audiocassette (38 minutes) + 1 transcript (18 typed leaves)
      Interview with Shirley Jones, singer for the Jones Girls; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 104
    - King, Alonzo, 1989 July 9, INT 84; cass 1364; 1 audiocassette (96 minutes) + 1 transcript (27 typed leaves)
      Interview with Alonzo King, record distributor; recorded in Chicago, Illinois.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 220--CDREF 221
    - Lanier, Warren, 1983 April 18, INT 91A--INT 91B; cass 1372--cass 1373; 2 audiocassettes (118 minutes) + 1 transcript (38 typed leaves)
      Interview with Warren Lanier, record promoter; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 232--CDREF 234
    - Lott, Robert and Jackie McNicholas, 1982 December 21, INT 26; cass 1278; 1 audiocassette (43 minutes) + 1 transcript (11 typed leaves)
      Interview with Robert Lott and Jackie McNicholas, producers for Gavin and Lott Associates; recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 105
    - Love, Billye, 1983 February 2, INT 27A--INT 27B; cass 1279--cass 1280; 2 audiocassettes (126 minutes) + 1 transcript (53 typed leaves)
      Interview with Billye Love, program manager and music director for WOKB Radio, Orlando; recorded in Orlando, Florida.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 106--CDREF 107
    - Love, Billye, 1982 March 25, [unnumbered]; cass 2669; 1 audiocassette
      Currently unavailable - Contact AAAMC staff for details
    - Love, Darlene, 1983 April 6, INT 28; cass 1281; 1 audiocassette (86 minutes) + 1 transcript (39 typed leaves)
      Interview with Darlene Love, vocalist and background singer for The Blossoms and Phil Spector Records; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 108--CDREF 109
    - Love, Walt, 1983 February 11, INT 29; cass 1282; 1 audiocassette (91 minutes) + 1 transcript (37 typed leaves) and supplementary materials
      Interview with Walt Love, disc jockey and staff editor for Radio and Records; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Supplementary materials consist of "R&B Black station master file listing" for Feb. 24, 1983; copies of the March 11 and 18, 1983 issues of Radio & Records; and two letters sent to WOKB from The Dixie Dance Kings and Mickey Turntable.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 110--CDREF 111
    - Mason, Barbara, 1982 September 30, INT 30A--INT 30D; cass 1283--cass 1286; 4 audiocassettes (197 minutes) + 1 transcript (70 typed leaves)
      Interview with Barbara Mason, producer and artist for Alpha Studios; recorded in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 112--CDREF 116
    - MaultsBy, Carl, 1981 November 30, INT 92A--INT 92B; cass 1374--cass 1375; 2 audiocassettes (97 minutes) + 1 transcript (24 typed leaves)
      Interview with Carl Maultsby, arranger, conductor, composer, instrumentalist, and former staff producer with RCA Records; recording location unknown.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 235--CDREF 237
    - McCoy, Sid, 1984 September 18, INT 31A--INT 31B; cass 1287--cass 1288; 2 audiocassettes (119 minutes) + 1 transcript (55 typed leaves)
      Interview with Sid McCoy, radio personality, disc jockey, and executive with Vee-Jay Records; recorded in Santa Monica, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 117--CDREF 119
    - McNicholas, Jackie
      SEE: Lott, Robert and Jackie McNicholas.
    - McRae, Joyce, undated, INT 93; cass 1376; 1 audiocassette (90 minutes) + 1 transcript (24 typed leaves)
      Interview with Joyce McRae, artist manager; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 238--CDREF 239
    - Medlin, Joe, 1982 November 22, INT 32A; cass 1289; 1 audiocassette (57 minutes) + 1 transcript (20 typed leaves)
      Interview with Joe Medlin, record executive for Polygram Records; recorded in New York, New York.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 120
    - Medlin, Joe, 1982 September 27, INT 32B; cass 1290; 1 audiocassette (67 minutes) + 1 transcript (24 typed leaves)
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 121
    - Moore, Sam, 1983 February 24, INT 33A--INT 33F; cass 1291--cass 1296; 6 audiocassettes (522 minutes) + 1 transcript (191 typed leaves) and supplementary materials
      Interview with Sam Moore, vocalist for Atlantic Records, Stax Records, and member of the vocal group Sam and Dave; recorded in New York, New York.
      Supplementary materials consist of biography and résumé from Celeb Research and a photocopy of a news clipping.
      Pagination for transcript restarts with cassette 1292 and then continues consecutively through the end of cass 1296 (i.e., 1-34; 1-155).
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 122--CDREF 132
    - Nuri, Erik, 1984 September 22, INT 41?; cass 1308; 1 audiocassette (14 minutes)
      Interview with Erik Nuri, music consultant and vice president of A&R for RCA and Arista Records.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 149
    - Otis, Johnny, 1984 September 13, INT 34; cass 1297; 1 audiocassette (95 minutes) + 1 transcript (36 typed leaves)
      Interview with Johnny Otis, bandleader, producer, songwriter, and composer; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 133--CDREF 134
    - Ott, Horace, 1982 November 28, INT 35; cass 1298; 1 audiocassette (70 minutes) + 1 transcript (26 typed leaves); Maultsby, Portia K.; Stephens, Robert
      Interview with Horace Ott, arranger and producer; recorded in Montclair, New Jersey.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 135
    - Parker, Deanie, 1984 September 6, INT 36A--INT 36C; cass 1299, 1301 (dup?); 1 audiocassette (138 minutes) + 1 transcript (57 typed leaves) and supplementary materials
      Interview with Deanie Parker, public relations for Stax Records; recorded in Memphis, Tennessee.
      Supplementary materials consist of news clippings and photocopies of news clippings related to Stax.
      Cass 1301 is a duplicate of most, if not all, of the content on cass 1299.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 136--CDREF 138
    - Reed, Tom, undated, INT 96; cass 1380; 1 audiocassette (92 minutes) + 1 transcript (31 typed leaves)
      Interview with Tom Reed, radio personality; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 244--CDREF 245
    - Rich, Jai, 1983 May 12, INT 97A--INT 97B; cass 1381--cass 1382; 2 audiocassettes (150 minutes)
      Interview with Jai Rich, sales for KJLH Radio; recorded in Los Angeles, California.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 246--CDREF 248
    - Rifkind, Jules, 1982 September 21, INT 37; cass 1302; 1 audiocassette (52 minutes) + 1 transcript (20 typed leaves)
      Interview with Jules Rifkind (aka Julie Rifkind), record executive and president for Spring Records; recorded in New York, New York.
      Pagination for transcript skips page 4.
      Compact disc(s): CDREF 139